Sabita Akter Koly

First Ladies Hall, SUST, Sylhet. 01604667584 | sabitaakterkoly23@gmail.com

Objective

Passionate and enthusiastic student with excellent interpersonal skills and a high interest in foreign diversity. To build up a career in a well- established and environment friendly organisation where acquired knowledge and expertise can be used effective and efficiently.

Experience

Institute of Development Affairs (IDEA)

December 2023 - March 2024

Internship

Worked on various projects like Enhancing Child Education in Tea Garden (ECETG), Advancing Women Rights of Access to Information in Bangladesh (AWRAIB), Accessing Learning Opportunities to the Young, Adolescents and Livelihood Options for Women (ALOY-ALOW) Project.

Key Learnings:

- Practical understanding of development work.
- Data collection, Social mapping, Data analysis and Reporting skills.
- Got chance to communicate within organisation and out of organisation such as with donor body, government officials, and local administration body.
- Got experience to involve in decision making process in organisation.
- Institute of Research Help Bangladesh (RHB)

February 2024 - May 2024

Member

Successful completion of three months online live training course on 'Research Methodology : Basic to Advanced' organised by Research Help Bangladesh.

Sonchalon
 November 2021 - March 2023

Executive Member

Connected with blood donation, blood supply, and other social development volunteer work.

Education

•	Shahjalal University of Science and Technology, Sylhet. Master of Social Science (MSS)	Ongoing
•	Shahjalal University of Science and Technology, Sylhet. Bachelor of Social Science (BSS) CGPA- 3.45 (Out of 4.00)	2022
•	Netrokona Govt. College Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC) GPA- 4.92 (Out of 5.00)	2018
•	Netrakona Govt Girls' High School Secondary School Certificate (SSC)	2016

Skills

- Software Support like MS word, MS excel, MS PowerPoint.
- Adaptability and problem solving.

GPA- 5 (Out of 5.00)

- Energetic, sincere, devoted and hardworking.
- Ability to motivate staff and maintain good relations.

Interests

• Travelling, Music, Photography, Creative Writing and other creative endeavors.

Languages

- Bengali
- English
- Hindi

Reference

Jahangir Alam - Metro Projects LTD
 Chief Executive Officer
 metroprojects.bd@gmail.com
 01722265124

• Nazmul Hoque - Institute of Development Affairs Executive Director

idea.sylhet@yahoo.com 01712176667